Tammy Batubo

tammy.batubo@gmail.com

dev-tam.com



https://github.com/devTam

PERSONAL PROFILE

Front-End Engineer

Experienced Software Developer with a specialty in Front End development. Proficient in HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, React as well as PHP and MySQL. Targeting a role as a Front End Developer to be a valuable asset in a great team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI Engineer - contract

Olla systems

Aug 2020 - Present

- Redesigned all pages of the solution in accordance to the style guide given
- Developed all pages including sign in, log in and password reset pages, vendors list and vendor pages.
- Refactored the code bases and routing to follow the design flow

Front-End developer Intern

Google Africa Development Scholarship

May 2020 - Present

- Built a fully responsive Progressive Weather Web App and deployed to firebase
- Reviewed web apps built by other team members and improved overall performance and web accessibility stats.
- Collaborated with team members to test solutions before deploying to production.
- Built an album store app with Angular

Front-End developer Intern

HNG Internship

May 2020 - Aug 2020

- Collaborated with Designers to build fully responsive websites and apps.
- Maintained an organized workflow using a project management tool (GitHub).
- · Tested to identify bugs and technical issues before and after deploying.
- Documented bug reports, tickets, and any code changes.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, HTML, CSS/Sass, PHP, GraphQL

Libraries & Frameworks

|Query, React, Gatsby, Next.js, Bootstrap, GSAP

Tools & Platforms

Git, Webpack, Netlify, Heroku, Firebase, Redux, react-redux, mySQL, VSCode, Apollo

Design

Adobe Xd, Figma

EDUCATION

Zero To Mastery Academy

The complete web development

University of Debrecen

Medicine - MBBS